<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Country Music on spacemule.net</title>
    <link>https://spacemule.net/categories/country-music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Country Music on spacemule.net</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 14:41:36 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://spacemule.net/categories/country-music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>These Bars</title>
      <link>https://spacemule.net/posts/these-bars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 14:41:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spacemule.net/posts/these-bars/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s my belief that a country song is not good because it&amp;rsquo;s good. It&amp;rsquo;s good because it&amp;rsquo;s a good country song. There is a Platonic ideal for a country song, and like Plato, the definition alludes me. While Steve Goodman may be crowned as king of the &amp;ldquo;perfect country and western song,&amp;rdquo; I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s right to bestow such an honored title in perpetuity. I also don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s right that See the Big Man Cry should even have to compete with a novelty song and He Stopped Loving Her Today.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s my belief that a country song is not good because it&amp;rsquo;s good. It&amp;rsquo;s good because it&amp;rsquo;s a good country song. There is a Platonic ideal for a country song, and like Plato, the definition alludes me. While Steve Goodman may be crowned as king of the &amp;ldquo;perfect country and western song,&amp;rdquo; I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s right to bestow such an honored title in perpetuity. I also don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s right that &lt;em&gt;See the Big Man Cry&lt;/em&gt; should even have to compete with a novelty song and &lt;em&gt;He Stopped Loving Her Today&lt;/em&gt;. It&amp;rsquo;s just not fair to Charlie. Yet, I still needed something to push me to right this wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On January 3, 2021, I was involved in a bicycle accident that tore my ACL and damaged my meniscus. I was presribed alternately Tramadex and Percocet for the pain of the recovery and reconstructive surgery. In the haze of pain killers, I used my time off from work to write the lyrics to a country song that I knew had to be written.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It seemed wrong&amp;mdash;given that bars are both a place where alcohol is served and a means of confinement&amp;mdash;that only songs like &lt;em&gt;Still Doing Time&lt;/em&gt; even touched on this obvious pun. I had to fill that void. This is my attempt:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;The lights come on, it&amp;#39;s time to go and settle the tab.
For all my lusts I&amp;#39;ve wound up here and given all I had.
With shaking limbs I get up and make my way to the chair.
I&amp;#39;ve no strength left to face the truth: Death is in the air.

[Chorus]
I&amp;#39;m stuck inside these bars,
Why do I act so proud?
I tell myself these lies
and wear pride as a shroud.
I&amp;#39;m stuck inside these bars
I&amp;#39;ll wish the world goodbye
I&amp;#39;m stuck inside these bars, and
I know that&amp;#39;s where I&amp;#39;ll die

I tell myself that I can change and make it come out right,
But change won&amp;#39;t come and I know I&amp;#39;ve taken my own life.
I try each day to show the world the image of a man,
and every night, behind these bars, I&amp;#39;m back where I began.

Five years ago we tied the knot. Who knew on just a thread?
Now she is gone and my home is this concrete bed. 
I stole her years with drunken lies and ended it the night
I told her she&amp;#39;d be better dead, and she said: &amp;#34;You&amp;#39;re right.&amp;#34;

[Chorus]

The time has come. The shaking&amp;#39;s gone. Fire&amp;#39;s in my throat.
I feel the cold on my hands and pray my soul to float
Far away from where I sit, sentenced to my death.
My resting place behind this bar with liquor on my breath.

I&amp;#39;m stuck inside these bars,
Why do I act so proud?
I tell myself these lies
and wear pride as a shroud.
I&amp;#39;m stuck inside these bars
I&amp;#39;ll wish the world goodbye
I&amp;#39;m stuck inside these bars, and
I know that here I&amp;#39;ll die
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
